Cooperative Recreation Service collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3. Production Files/Custom Songbook Files, ca. 1932-2008
  - Seal of Ohio Girl Scout Council (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1995-1996 (Box-folder 88/8)
    Includes Music Shall Live: Girl Scout Songbook, as well as related song indexes, lists, correspondence, and permissions for Kum Ba Yah from Marvin V. Frey as well in addition to other permissions.
  - Seal of Ohio Girl Scout Council (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1995-1996 (Box-folder 88/9)
    Includes Music Shall Live: Girl Scout Songbook, custom songbook and song master negatives for the songbook.
  - Pete Seeger (W.A.S.), ca. 1982-1986 (Box-folder 88/10)
    Includes correspondence and a 1982 issue of the Sing Out! Bulletin.
  - Pete Seeger, correspondence, ca. 1956-1958 (Box-folder 88/11)
    Correspondence to and from Pete Seeger, Joe Hickerson, Augustus Zanzig, and Mary Tolbert.
  - Seiwa College, ca. 1986-1993 (Box-folder 88/12)
    Correspondence and permissions information with and relating to Seiwa College for Christian Workers in Japan.
  - Set lists for songbooks, ca. 1965-1970 (Box-folder 89/1)
    Includes lists of sets, songs, locations, and names.
  - Seven Lakes Girl Scout Council (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1981-1992 (Box-folder 89/2)
    Includes Seven Lakes Songbook custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, notes, permissions information, song lists, and song sheets.
  - Seven Lakes Girl Scout Council (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1964-1979 (Box-folder 89/3)
    Includes correspondence, cover designs, ordering material, song indexes, and song sheets.
  - Sierra Club book permissions (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1981-1985 (Box-folder 89/4)
    Book designs, permissions, correspondence, notes, and sheet music related to the Sierra Club custom songbook.
  - Sierra Club book permissions (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1976-1979 (Box-folder 89/5)
    Correspondence, notes, and price estimages for the Sierra Club custom song book.
  - Sierra Club songbook (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1971-1978 (Box-folder 89/6)
    Song lists, correspondence, and permission information about the Sierra Club custom songbook.
  - Sierra Club songbook (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1977 (Box-folder 89/7)
    Correspondence and permission information about the Sierra Club custom song book.
  - Sing a Tune (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1978-1984 (Box-folder 89/8)
    Correspondence, permission information, and sheet music about the Sing a Tune custom songbook.
  - Sing a Tune (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1963-1967 (Box-folder 90/1)
    Correspondence, song lists, and notes related to the Sing a Tune custom song book.
  - Sing Again and Again (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1978 (Box-folder 90/2)
    Copyright, permissions and copyright information, correspondence, shipping information, and notes relating to the Sing Again and Again custom song book.
  - Sing Again and Again (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1977-1978 (Box-folder 90/3)
  - Sing Around the World, ca. 1965-1969 (Box-folder 90/4)
    Includes Sing Around the World custom songbook and related song indexes.
  - Sing For Joy, ca. 1977-1978 (Box-folder 90/5)
    Notes and correspondence related to the Sing For Joy custom songbook.
  - Sing It Again, ca. 1962-1970 (Box-folder 90/6)
    Two copies of Sing it Again custom songbook, as well as related song master negatives, correspondence, and song indexes.
  - Singing the Lord's Song, 1989 edition, 1989 (Box-folder 90/7)
    Royalty payment information, correspondence, and licenses related to the 1989 edition of Singing the Lord's Song.
  - Singing the Lord's Song, 1991 edition, 1991 (Box-folder 90/8)
    Royalty payment information, correspondence, and licenses related to the 1991 edition of Singing the Lord's Song.
  - Singing the Lord's Song, 3rd/4th printing (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1984-1986 (Box-folder 90/9)
    Includes correspondence, permissions, publishing, and licensing information related to the Singing the Lord's Song custom songbook.
  - Singing the Lord's Song, 3rd/4th printing (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 90/10)
    Shipping information, correspondence, and permission information related to the Singing the Lord's Song custom songbook.
  - Singing the Lord's Song, 4th printing, ca. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 90/11)
    Includes Singing the Lord's Song custom songbook, as well as related correspondence and license, permissions, publishing, and copyright information.
  - Singing the Lord's Song royalties, ca. 1988-1989 (Box-folder 90/12)
    Includes correspondence and license, permissions, publishing, and copyright information.
  - Singing the Lord's Song (Methodist Men edition), ca. 1980-1983 (Box-folder 91/1)
    Includes Singing the Lord's Song: United Methodist Men custom songbook, as well as drafts of the songbook, correspondence and license, copyright, and publishing information.
  - Song check lists, undated (Box-folder 91/2)
    Song information, and check lists of plates in songbooks.
  - Songbook copies (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 91/3)
    Includes song sheets and notes in preparation for custom songbooks.
  - Songbook copies (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 91/4)
  - Songbook reports and order forms (1 of 4), ca. 1965-1966 (Box-folder 91/5)
    Songbook reports for custom songbooks, including numbers of copies printed and favorite songs.
  - Songbook reports and order forms (2 of 4), undated (Box-folder 91/6)
  - Songbook reports and order forms (3 of 4), undated (Box-folder 91/7)
    Songbook reports for custom songbooks, including catalogs, order forms, numbers of copies printed and favorite songs.
  - Songbook reports and order forms (4 of 4), undated (Box-folder 91/8)
  - Songs and typesetting, part of Singing the Lord's Song, undated (Box-folder 92/1)
    Includes song sheets and typesetting examples, song indexes, and song master negatives.
  - Songs and Creations, undated (Box-folder 92/2)
    Song workshop and song leading information.
  - Songs for Camp, Jefferson County Public Schools (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 92/3)
    Includes Music for the Mountains (Songs From Our Heritage) custom songbook, as well as related publishing information, correspondence, permissions, song lists, and notes.
  - Songs for Camp, Jefferson County Public Schools (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 92/4)
    Includes correspondence with Jefferson County Public Schools staff, as well as song sheets and publishing information.
  - Songs for Camp, Jefferson County Public Schools (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1976-1977 (Box-folder 92/5)
    Includes Songs for Camp custom songbook, as well as related notes, correspondence, and publishing information.
  - Songs for United Methodists Men, ca. 1977 (Box-folder 92/6)
    Includes copies of Songs for Methodist Men custom songbook, as well as related notes, correspondence, and publishing information.
  - Songs of Many Nations (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1966 (Box-folder 92/7)
    Includes Songs of Many Nations custom songbook, a cover design sketch, and song master negatives, as well as related correspondence and notes.
  - Songs of Many Nations (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1965 (Box-folder 92/8)
    Includes two copies of Songs of Many Nations custom songbook, as well as song lists, indexes, song sheets, and correspondence.
  - Songs of Sharing, Betty Dale, ca. 1981-1983 (Box-folder 93/1)
    Copyright form and related information, song lists, and correspondence related to Songs of Sharing custom songbook and the National Council on Aging.
  - Songs of the Wigwam, ca. 1955 (Box-folder 93/2)
    Includes copies of Songs of the Wigwam custom songbook and related song lists and copyright information.
  - Songs sent to W.R. Music Service, ca. 2000-2002 (Box-folder 93/3)
    Includes song sheets, song indexes, and communication with W.R. Music Service.
  - Songs to Keep, ca. 1965-1972 (Box-folder 93/4)
    Includes copies of Songs to Keep custom songbook, as well as song sheets, song indexes, correspondence, book design materials, and other publishing information.
  - Songs to Sing Again and Again (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1981-1996 (Box-folder 93/5)
    Correspondence, permissions, and copyright information related to the Songs to Sing Again and Again custom songbook.
  - Songs to Sing Again and Again (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1981-1985 (Box-folder 93/6)
    Correspondence, permissions, copyright information, notes, and publication information related to the Songs to Sing Again and Again custom songbook. Includes correspondence with the Library of Congress Archive of Folk Song.
  - South Central Alabama Sings, ca. 1964-1979 (Box-folder 93/7)
    Correspondence, song lists, song indexes, and permissions information related to the South Central Sings custom songbook.
  - Spirituals (Foley), ca. 1968-1969 (Box-folder 93/8)
    Correspondence, song lists, song master negatives, and permissions and publishing information related to the Sprituals custom songbook (includes two copies).
  - Spruce Lake, ca. 1988 (Box-folder 93/9)
    Correspondence, permissions, licensing information, song lists, and other publishing information related to the Spruce Lake Retreat custom songbooks.
  - Stock songbook; African Songs; Reprint, 1958, 1996 (Box-folder 93/10)
    Includes African Songs custom songbook, as well as song sheets and song master negatives.
  - Summy-Birchard Company, ca. 1978-1981 (Box-folder 93/11)
    Includes correspondence and copyright information related to the "Songbook for Iowa Methodists."
  - Sunshine ("May There Always Be Sunshine"), ca. 1965 (Box-folder 93/12)
    Research, correspondence, and a drawing related to the song "May There Always Be Sunshine."
  - SW Pennsylvania Girl Scouts (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1978-1981 (Box-folder 94/1)
    Includes Sing Scout Sing custom songbook and related correspondence, permissions, and publishing information.
  - SW Pennsylvania Girl Scouts (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1964-1978 (Box-folder 94/2)
    Includes correspondence, permissions, copyright information, song master negatives related to the Sing Scout Sing custom songbook and the Girl Scouts of Southwestern Pennsylvania.
  - Swiss Alpine Songs, ca. 1956-1957, 1991 (Box-folder 94/3)
    Includes Swiss Alpine Songs custom songbook, as well as related correspondence with the Swiss National Tourist Office and Hug & Foetisch Musique.
  - Talus Rock Girl Scouts Sing, ca. 1998-1999 (Box-folder 94/4)
    Includes song lyrics and song sheets related to the Talus Rock Girl Scouts Sing custom songbook.
  - Tayo'y Umawit - Let's Sing! (Philippines), ca. 1979 (Box-folder 94/5)
    Includes Tayo'y Umawit - Let's Sing! custom songbook and related song sheets, correspondence, and permissions information.
  - Fran Thomas (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1962-1964 (Box-folder 94/6)
    Includes correspondence with composer Frances Thomas and sheet music.
  - Fran Thomas (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1959-1963 (Box-folder 94/7)
  - Janet Tobitt, correspondence (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1955-1961 (Box-folder 94/8)
    Correspodence with Janet Tobitt of Girl Scouts of the United States of America and Lynn Rohrbough.
  - Janet Tobitt, correspondence (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1960-1970 (Box-folder 94/9)
    Correspodence with Janet Tobitt of Girl Scouts of the United States of America and Lynn Rohrbough, and songbooks compiled by Janet Tobitt, such as Folk Songs of the East.
  - Mary Tolbert, ca. 1964-1970 (Box-folder 94/10)
    Includes correspondence with music educator, Mary Tolbert, and My Pocket Paul of 88 Songs custom songbook.
  - Top Score, ca. 1967-1968 (Box-folder 95/1)
    Includes copies of Top Score custom songbook, as well as song sheets, song master negatives, song lists, and correspondence.
  - Trinidad-Tobago Play Party Book (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1961 (Box-folder 95/2)
    Inlcudes correspondence, song research, and notes related to the Trinidad-Tobago Play Party Book.
  - Trinidad-Tobago Play Party Book (folder 2 of 2), ca, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 95/3)
    Includes selections of sheet music and dance and game instruction from Five Folk Songs (Singing Games) of the Caribbean by J.D. Elder.
  - United Council of Churches (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1983-1992 (Box-folder 95/4)
    Includes copies of Seed Songs of Earth and Spirit by Jim Manley as well as related publication, correspondence, and shipping information.
  - United Council of Churches (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1973-1983 (Box-folder 95/5)
    Includes publication materials related to Seed Songs of Earth and Spirit, as well as other publications by Jim Manley.
  - University of Maryland (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1978-1981 (Box-folder 95/6)
    Includes Tunes for Terrapins: The UMCP Songbook custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, rights and permissions information, song sheets, and song master negatives.
  - University of Maryland (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1977-1981 (Box-folder 95/7)
    Book designs, sheet music, and correspondence related to the Tunes for Terrapins: The UMCP Songbook custom songbook.
  - University of Oregon book (Dr. Harrison), ca. 1977 (Box-folder 95/8)
    Includes sheet music, notes, and correspondence with Dr. Lois N. Harrison of University of Oregon School of Music.
  - Various dances and quadrilles, undated (Box-folder 98/6)
    Sheet music for dances.
  - Various dances and quadrilles, undated (Box-folder 98/7)
  - Vermont, ca. 1959-1967 (Box-folder 95/9)
    Includes copies of Vermont Sings custom songbook, as well as related indexes, song master negatives, notes, and correspondence from the State of Vermont Board of Recreation, Montpelier.
  - We Shall Overcome, 1984 (Box-folder 96/1)
    Paper titled "Notes by Robin on phone conversation with Guy Carawan, July 17, 1984" about the origins of the song "We Shall Overcome."
  - Weiss book reprint, ca. 1986-1991 (Box-folder 96/2)
    Correspondence and permissions information related to Evelyn Weiss and the Peace Songbook.
  - Evelyn Weiss, ca. 1983 (Box-folder 96/3)
    Includes sheet music relating to Evelyn Weiss publications.
  - West Virginia 4-H (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1982-1984 (Box-folder 96/4)
    Correspondence, song lists, song sheets, song indexes, and permissions information related to the West Virginia 4-H custom songbook.
  - West Virginia 4-H (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1961-1983 (Box-folder 96/5)
    Correspondence, song lists, song sheets, song indexes, song master negatives, and copyright, permissions, and publication information related to the West Virginia 4-H custom songbook.
  - Westering Home (song), ca. 1980 (Box-folder 96/6)
    Permissions information related to the song "Westering Home."
  - Western Massachusetts Girl Scout Council, ca. 1980-1985 (Box-folder 96/7)
    Correspondence, permissions, and copyright information related to the songbook for the Western Massachusetts Girl Scout Council.
  - Bliss Wiant, ca. 1956-1970 (Box-folder 96/8)
    Includes The American Guild of Organists Youngstown Chapter Presents: Hymns in a World Community custom songbook, as well as correspondence with Bliss and Mildred Wiant of Chung Chi College.
  - Helen Wing, children's songs, ca. 1969-1970 (Box-folder 96/9)
    Includes song sheets by composer, Helen Wing, song master negatives, and correspondence.
  - Work and Sing, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 96/10)
    Correspondence with Irwin Abrams of the American Friends Service Committee and others, as well as song research, lists, and other publication information.
  - Work and Sing, Hans-Peter Muller, ca. 1954-1958 (Box-folder 96/11)
    Correspondence, permission, and publication information from Hans-Peter Muller of the Co-ordination Committee for International Voluntary Work Camps c/o Youth Section, UNESCO.
  - Work and Sing, International Contacts (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1951-1954 (Box-folder 96/12)
    Correspondence with individuals and organizations around the world relating to Cooperative Recreation Service song and game books.
  - Work and Sing, International Contacts (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1947-1952 (Box-folder 97/1)
    Correspondence with individuals and organizations around the world relating to the Work and Sing custom songbook and other Cooperative Recreation Service song and game books.
  - Work and Sing, International Contacts (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1948-1951 (Box-folder 97/2)
  - Work and Sing, YMCA Paris, ca. 1955-1963 (Box-folder 97/3)
    Includes copies of Work and Sing: an International Songbook custom songbook as well as related correspondence and publication information.
  - John W. Work, ca. 1948-1958 (Box-folder 97/4)
    Articles about Lynn Rohrbaugh and Cooperative Recreation Service, and correspondence with Fisk University professor John W. Work.
  - YWCA dances (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 97/5)
    Sheet music with dance movement instruction of dances from around the world.
  - YWCA dances (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 97/6)
  - Augustus D. Zanzig (folder 1 of 4), ca. 1965-1972 (Box-folder 97/7)
    Correspondence with Augustus D. Zanzig about Cooperative Recreation Service and song selections for custom songbooks.
  - Augustus D. Zanzig (folder 2 of 4), ca. 1965-1968 (Box-folder 97/8)
    Correspondence with Augustus D. Zanzig, song lists, and other information about songs, dances, and game books.
  - Augustus D. Zanzig (folder 3 of 4), ca. 1964-1967 (Box-folder 97/9)
    Correspondence with Augustus D. Zanzig, song lists, song sheets, and other information about songs, dances, and game books.
  - Augustus D. Zanzig (folder 4 of 4), ca. 1965-1970 (Box-folder 98/1)
    Includes correspondence, song lists, and samplers of poetry and sayings Augustus sent to Cooperative Recreation Service for consideration.
  - Augustus Zanzig, correspondence (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1961-1965 (Box-folder 98/2)
    Correspondence regarding publication information for custom songbooks.
  - Augustus Zanzig, correspondence (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1959-1960 (Box-folder 98/3)
    Correspondence regarding song selections for custom songbooks.
  - Augustus Zanzig, correspondence (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1958-1963 (Box-folder 98/4)
    Correspondence and song suggestions for custom songbooks.
  - Zebe Publishing, Germany, ca. 1998 (Box-folder 98/4)
    Correspondence with Zebe Publishing, a music publishing company in Hamburg, Germany, asking permissions to print a C.R.S. custom songbook in Europe.
- Series 4. Song indexes and copyright research, ca. 1930-1970
  Research materials for custom songbooks. Song index lists and cards include geographic origins, language, musical type, and copyright status of each song. Includes permissions and copyright registrations.
  - Copyrights (index cards), undated (Box-folder 102/1)
    Alphabetical index cards of song titles and which custom songbook each song is associated with, year of publication, and composer information.
  - Copyrights, A-K (permissions granted to CRS by others), undated (Box-folder 100/1)
    Alphabetical list of songs and permissions requested and granted for each song for Cooperative Recreation custom songbooks.
  - Copyrights, L-Z (permissions granted to CRS by others), undated (Box-folder 100/2)
  - Fillers, Graces, Rounds, etc. (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 100/3)
    Sheet music for short pieces.
  - Fillers, Graces, Rounds, etc. (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 100/4)
  - Geographic classifications (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 100/5)
    Alphabetical listing of countries and their associated songs.
  - Geographic classifications (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 100/6)
  - Paid permissions, undated (Box-folder 102/2)
    Alphabetical index cards of song titles, publishing companies, and dates.
  - Records of CRS copyrights, undated (Box-folder 100/7)
    Alphabetical list of songs and associated copyright registrations and application information.
  - Song copyright holders and other copyright information, undated (Box-folder 100/8)
    Index of copyright songs, owners, and royalties, as well as copyright research materials.
  - Song index, copy 1 (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 101/1)
    Alphabetical listing of songs, geographic origins, language, musical type, and copyright status.
  - Song index, copy 1 (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 101/2)
  - Song index, copy 2 (folder 1 of 2), undated (Box-folder 101/3)
  - Song index, copy 2 (folder 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 101/4)
  - Song index cards, A-H (folder 1 of 3), undated (Box-folder 101/5)
    Alphabetical index cards with song titles and custom songbook associated with each song.
  - Song index cards, I-Q (folder 2 of 3), undated (Box-folder 101/6)
  - Song index cards, R-Z (folder 3 of 3), undated (Box-folder 101/7)
  - Song list, undated (Box-folder 101/8)
    Alphabetical list of song titles, copyright status, and song type.
Published materials
Published songbooks, both by World Around Songs, as well as by other publishers that served as research and reference materials for the publishing company.
Around The Campfire: Australian Guide Song Book. Australia: Girl Guides Association of Australia, 1985.
YWCA Camp Newaygo. Camp Newaygo Sings. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, 1986.
NCCS Camp Newaygo. Camp Newaygo Sings II. Michigan: n.p., 2001.
World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts. Canciones de Nuestra Cabaῆa.: n.p., 1980.
Johnson, David N. Carols of Many Lands. vol. 3. Minneapolis: Augsburg Publishing House, 1982.
Glamble, Alan. Chanté Domnitjen: Folks Songs of Dominica. Roseau, Dominica: Dominica Institute, 1986.
Weiss, Evelyn. Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet. 3rd print. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, 1986.
Duy, Pham. Dân Ca Folk Songs. Saigon, Vietnam: Melody Trails, 1966.
Herman, Michael. Folk Dance Syllabus number one. New York: Folk Dance House, 1953.
Bidstrup, Georg and Marguerite. Folk Dances: brought from Denmark by Georg & Marguerite Bidstrup. North Carolina: The Stephens Press, 1952.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. III No. 2. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1982.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. III No. 3. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1983.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. IV No. 1. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1983.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. IV No. 2. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1984.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. IV No. 3. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1984.
Scott, John A. and Laurence I. Seidman, eds. Folksong in the Classroom. Vol. V No. 2. Newark, NJ: n.p., 1985.
World Conference of Friends. Friends Sing in Spirit and in Truth. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, 1991.
Harris, Frank W.. Games. 5th ed. Sunnyvale, California: n.p., 1982.
Great Valley Girl Scout Council Songbook. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, n.d.
Great Valley Songbook. 2nd ed. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, n.d.
Larry Eisenberg. Joyful Noise. Burnsville, NC: World Around Songs, 1989.
Amidon, Peter and Mary Alice Amidon. Jump Jim Joe. Battleboro, Vermont: New England Dancing Masters Productions, 1991.
Minnesota 4-H Songbook. St. Paul, MN: University of Minnesota, 1970.
Of Play and Playfulness. Millmont, PA: Eastern Cooperative Recreation School, 1990.
Friends of Pax Lodge Committee. Pax Lodge Songbook. London: World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts, 2004.
Tobitt, Janet E. Promenade All. New York: n.p., 1947.
Friends of Sangam Committee, USA. Sangam Sangeet: Sangam Songbook. New York: Girl Scouts of the U.S.A., 1997.
Manley, Jim. Seed Songs of Earth and Spirit. Burnsville, North Carolina: World Around Songs, 1983.
Carolina Farm Stewardship Association. Sing the Good Earth. Pittsboro, NC: Carolina Farm Stewardship Association, 1982.
Singing Games and Folk Dances. Brasstown, NC: John Campbell Folk School, 1941.
Songs from our Heritage. 2nd ed. Palos Verdes Estates, CA: Palos Verdes Peninsula Unified School District, 1995.
Culliman, Esther. The Booklady. Burnsville, NV: World Around Songs, 1982.
Tobitt, Janet E. The Ditty Bag. New York: n.p., 1946.